(Music)
(موسيقى)
Sophie Hawley-Weld: OK, you don't have to stand up,
سوفي هولي-ويلد: حسنا، لستم في حاجة للوقوف،
but ...
لكن ...
we can see you really clearly --
نستطيع رؤيتكم بوضوح تام --
(Laughter)
(ضحك)
So you have to dance with us.
لذلك عليكم الرقص معنا.
And we have this, like,
ولدينا هذه، هكذا،
choreographed dance thing that we're about to do --
رقصة مُصَمَّمة سنقوم بها حالا --
Betta Lemme: Really easy.
بيتا ليمي: سهلة للغاية.
SHW: And we're going to flick our wrists like this,
سوفي: سنقوم بتحريك معصمنا هكذا،
and you're going to do it with us.
وستقومون بذلك معنا.
And you can also stand up.
ويمكنكم أيضًا الوقوف.
(Music)
(موسيقى)
(Sings) I know I did not raise a wrist
(تغني) أعلم أنني لم أرفع معصمي
(Both sing) I know I did not capture it
(تغنيان معا) أعلم أنني لم أمسكه
It came, it came,
لقد أتى، أتى،
it went, it went
وذهب، ذهب
It conquered quick
وتَغلَّب سريعًا
I was there and then I quit
كنت هناك ثم انسَحبْت
Awoo!
أووو!
I know I did not raise a wrist
أعلم أنني لم أرفع معصمي
I know I did not capture it
أعلم أنني لم أمسكه
It came, it came,
لقد أتى، أتى،
it went, it went
وذهب، ذهب
It conquered quick
وتَغلَّب سريعًا
I was there and then I quit
كنت هناك ثم انسَحبْت
Awoo!
أووو!
BL: (Speaks) There you go!
بيتا: (متحدثة) هكذا!
(Music)
(موسيقى)
SHW: We have another one coming up.
سوفي: لدينا حركة أخرى قادمة.
It's a little finger-pointing dance.
رقصة بسيطة بالإشارة بالأصبع.
(Music)
(موسيقى)
The people sitting down,
الناس الجالسون،
I want to see your fingers pointing.
أريد أن أراكم تشيرون بأصابعكم.
Yeah!
نعم!
(Sings) I know I did not raise a wrist
(تغني) أعلم أنني لم أرفع معصمي
(Both sing) I know I did not capture it
(تغنيان معا) أعلم أنني لم أمسكه
It came, it came,
لقد أتى، أتى،
it went, it went
وذهب، ذهب
It conquered quick
وتَغلَّب سريعًا
I was there and then I quit
كنت هناك ثم انسَحبْت
Aaaa ...
أه ه ه ه ...
(Applause)
(تصفيق)
Awoo!
أووو!
(Music)
(موسيقى)
(Clapping to the beat)
(تصفيق يواكب الإيقاع)
Aaaa ...
أ ه ه ه ه ...
SHW: (Speaks) Alright, hand flick.
سوفي: (متحدثة) حسنا، ضرب باليد.
(Both sing) I know I did not raise a wrist
(تغنيان) أعلم أنني لم أرفع معصمي
I know I did not capture it
أعلم أنني لم أمسكه
It came, it came,
لقد أتى، أتى،
it went, it went
وذهب، ذهب
It conquered quick
وتَغلَّب سريعًا
I was there and then I quit
كنت هناك ثم انسَحبْت
I know I did not raise a wrist
أعلم أنني لم أرفع معصمي
I know I did not capture it
أعلم أنني لم أمسكه
It came, it came,
لقد أتى، أتى،
it went, it went
وذهب، ذهب
It conquered quick
وتَغلَّب سريعًا
I was there and then I quit
كنت هناك ثم انسَحبْت
(Music)
(موسيقى)
Tucker Halpern: You guys are way more fun than I thought you'd be.
توكر هولبرن: أنتم أكثر مرحًا مما توقعت.
(Laughter)
(ضحك)
(Music)
(موسيقى)
Awoo!
أووو!
(Applause)
(تصفيق)
SHW: Thank you so much.
سوفي: أشكركم شكرا جزيلا.